Welcome to System Integration,
システム統合へようこそ
the final module of the Udacity self-driving car nanodegree program.
Ufacity　自動運転車　Naodegree プログラムの最終授業です。
Over the course of this program,
このプログラムのコースでは
you've built the major components of an autonomous vehicle system.
自動運転車両システムの主要コンポーネントを構築してきました
In this module, we'll be discussing the system architecture used in
このモジュールでは Udacity 自動運転車で使用するシステムアーキテクチャーについてお話することで
the Udacity self-driving car so that you can fit all of the pieces together.
すべてのパーツを組み合わせることが可能になります
Karla, the Udacity self-driving car,
Karla という Udacity 自動運転車には
has four major subsystems.
4 つの主要サブシステムが搭載されています
The first subsystem is the sensor subsystem,
最初のサブシステムはセンサーサブシステムであり
which consists of the hardware components that gather data about the environment.
環境に関するデータを集めるハードウェアコンポーネントで構成されています
This subsystem includes LIDAR,
このシステムにはライダー
radar, cameras, and even GPS sensors mounted on the car.
レーダー カメラ 車に取り付けられた GPS センサーも搭載しています
The second subsystem, the perception subsystem,
2 つめのサブシステムは 認識サブシステムであり
consists of software to process sensor data.
センサーデータを処理するソフトウェアで構成されています
You've built components of this subsystem already.
このサブシステムのコンポーネントについては 既に構築してあります
Components in the perception subsystem combine sensor data into meaningful information.
認識サブシステムのコンポーネントはセンサーデータをまとめて有意義な情報にします
The planning subsystem is the third subsystem on the vehicle.
プランニングサブシステムは車両の 3 つめのサブシステムです
The planning subsystem uses the output from perception for
プランニングサブシステムは挙動プランニングおよび短距離や長距離プランニングの
behavior planning and for both short and long range path planning.
認知からの出力結果を使用します
The final subsystem is the control subsystem,
最後のサブシステムは制御サブシステムで
which ensures that the vehicle follows the path provided by
車両がプランニングサブシステムに提供された経路をたどり
the planning subsystem and sends control commands to the vehicle.
制御コマンドを車両に送ります
As we'll see, information generally flows through the sub-systems from left to right,
ご覧いただくように 情報はサブシステムを左から右へ流れ
starting with sensor input and ending with control commands for the vehicle.
車両のセンサー入力から始まり 制御コマンドで終了します
As we go through this lesson,
この講義では
we'll go into more detail about
各サブシステムの詳細にふれ
each subsystem and how it connects to the rest of the vehicle.
それがどのように車両と結びつくのかを見ていきます